Guide to the Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
Fleming, Bryant plans
- Series I. Clients A-H
  - Carrier, Robert M. Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - Planting plan of the garden, 1913 (Folder 10)
      Sheet # 112
    - General planting plan, 1913 (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1038
      Condition:Good, Oversized
    - Detail planting plans of Herbaceous borders, 1913 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1049
    - Plan for planting about the overlook and entrance gates, 1913 (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1050
  - Location: Memphis, Tennessee
    - Details of double hung windows and door frames for service wing, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1039
      Scale: Full
    - Sleeping porch windows, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1040
      Scale: 3/4"=1'; Full
    - Details of type "D" windows and door from living porch for terrace, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1041
    - Detail for Gate post cap, Undated (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1042
      Condition:Unspecified
    - Details of Stair window, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1043
    - Details of Stone trim - Dining room and living porch windows, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1044
    - Details of doors and frames, Undated (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1045
    - Details of stone frames for Living room bay, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1046
      Scale: 1/2"=1'; Full
    - Details of window no. D-121, 1923 (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1047
    - Sketch detail of sundial, Undated (Folder 37)
      Sheet # 1048
    - Window measurements on elevations, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1051
      Note:By Crittail Casement Window Company
    - Window elevations and details, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1052
    - Window details, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1053
    - Window details, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1054
    - Window sections, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1055
    - Window sections, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1056
    - Window details, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1057
    - Details of door J-127 and screens, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1058
    - Stone and construction details (Arches in entrance hall), 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1059
    - Interior details - Kitchen and pantries, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1060
    - Door details, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1061
    - Interior details - Bathrooms # 3 and 4, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1062
    - Construction details, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1063
    - Interior elevations - Ante room, 1923 (Box 37)
      Sheet # 1064
    - Details of cupboards in kitchen and pantries, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1065
    - Detail of balustrade, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1066
    - Elevations of men's wardrobe - Closet in Bath #1, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1067
    - Detail of marble console for women's room, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1068
    - Elevations of men's and women's dressing room, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1069
    - Elevations and details of inner hall, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1070
    - Interior details - Sleeping porch, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1071
    - Interior details - Mrs. Carrier's dressing room, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1072
    - Interior details - Living porch, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1073
    - Interior details - Bedroom #4, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1074
    - Elevations of leaded glass - Second floor, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1075
    - Leaded glass - First floor, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1076
    - Details of typical plank frame windows, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1077
    - Details of newel post for main stair at second floor, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1078
    - Details - Mrs. Carrier's bedroom, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1079
    - Details - Mrs. Carrier's bedroom, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1080
    - Cut stone details, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1081
    - Detail of brick walks, 1923 (Box 38)
      Sheet # 1082
      Scale: 1/4"=1'; 3/4"=1'
    - Linen room details, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1083
    - Chimney details, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1084
    - Stone fireplace details, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1085
    - Reflected ceiling plan - Living room, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1086
    - Details of Radiator Grilles, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1087
    - Details of Grilles in entrance hall, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1088
      Scale: 3/4"=1'; 3"=1'
    - Interior details - Bathrooms # 1 and 2, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1089
    - Interior details - Bedrooms # 2 and 3, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1090
    - Details of cupboard - Dressing room #2, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1091
    - Detail of paneling in rear hall and stair, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1092
    - First floor detail of paneling in rear hall, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1093
    - Details of cupboard on main stairs, 1923 (Box 39)
      Sheet # 1094
    - Perspective of study and west elevation, Sketch plan of dining room, loggia and study, Undated (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1095
      Format: Mounted tracing paper (Pencil and Crayon)
    - Perspective sketch- Guest's sitting room, Undated (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1097
    - Perspective sketch of east elevation, Undated (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1098
    - Perspective sketch of west elevation, Undated (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1099
    - Perspective sketch of dining room, Undated (Folder 38)
      Sheet # 1100
    - Second floor plan, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1101
    - Second floor plan - Scheme "C", 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1102
    - Second floor plan - Scheme "A", 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1103
    - Second floor plan - Scheme "B", 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1104
    - First floor plan - Scheme "B", 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1105
    - First floor plan - Scheme "C", 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1106
    - First floor plan, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1107
    - First floor plan, 1922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1108
  - Location: Sarvis, Mississippi
    - Memo sketch - Treatment of boys property, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1096
  - Chapin, Roy D. Location: Grosse Pointe, Michigan
    - Detailed plan of curved-wall garden, 1928 (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1417
    - Sketches and perspective of ironwork, 1928 (Folder 43b)
      Sheet # 1418
  - Cheek, Leslie Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - Maintenance gates and gate lodge, 1929 (Folder 53)
      Sheet # 2000
  - Chevy Chase Country Club Location: Chevy Chase, Maryland
    - Sketch showing location of Back nets for Tennis courts, 1910 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 230
      Scale: 40'=1"
    - Planting Plan, 1913 (Folder 14)
      Sheet # 232
      Condition:Fair, Oversized
    - General Plan showing terrace, walls, balustrade, steps, etc., 1913 (Folder 14)
      Sheet # 233
      Scale: 1/8=1"
    - 1/4" scale details of walls, balustrades, steps, and entrance gates about Clubhouse, 1913 (Folder 14)
      Sheet # 234
    - Scale details of walls, balustrades, steps, and entrance gates about Clubhouse, 1913 (Folder 14)
      Sheet # 235
  - Chopin, Roy/Ray P. Location: Grosse Pointe, Michigan
    - Sketch for entrance, corner of White and Cathey avenues, Junior League Home for Crippled children (H.S.), 1929 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1720
    - Sketch looking west in test gardens showing brick terminus for gardens (H. S.), 1928 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1721
  - Clark, Stephen C. Location: Cooperstown, New York (some specify Fernleigh)
    - Layout of Residence and Grounds, 1925 (Folder 42a)
      Sheet # 1397
    - Curved-wall, Posts, Wall, Planting, Undated (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1398
    - View from upper cottage walk, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1399
    - View from North and South walk, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1400
    - View from Garden terrace, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1401
    - Landscape design of gardens, Undated (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1722
      Format: Tracing paper, Some color
    - "Fernleigh"- view along studio walk, 1925 (Box 49)
      Sheet # 1723
    - "Fernleigh"- view from garden walk, 1925 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 1724
  - Clements, Mr. & Mrs. C. R. Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - Sketch, arrival court, Front of residence, 1930 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1395
    - Preliminary plans for development, 1930 (Folder 47)
      Sheet # 1683
      Format: Stock, colored
    - Perspective sketch D - Shelter at North end (H. S.), 1930 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1714
    - Perspective sketch B - Rock garden looking towards entrance court (H. S.), 1930 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1715
    - Perspective sketch F - Entrance treatment at Jackson Boulevard (H. S.), 1930 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1716
    - Perspective sketch F - terraces from residence at south west (H. S.), 1930 (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1717
  - Clement, S. M. Location: East Aurora, New York
    - Study of park, 1906 (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1696
    - Study of park, 1906 (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1830
    - Rough Sketch, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1831
    - Description unspecified, 1906 (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1832
    - Study for a garden, 1904 (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1833
    - Rough sketch of park, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1834
    - Rough sketch of park, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1835
    - Drawing of grounds, Undated (Box 64)
      Sheet # 1845
    - Planting (plantations), Sketch plan, 1903 (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1846
      Scale: 1"=10'; 1/16"=1'
    - Grounds, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1847
    - Study for a garden, 1904 (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1848
      Format: Sepia and negative
    - Study for a garden, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1849
    - Geometric configurations - planting plan, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1850
    - Description unspecified, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1851
  - Coonley, Avery Location: Riverside, Illinois
    Includes plans for Coonley House by Frank Llyod Wright.
    - Planting lists, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1561
      Format: Legal Sheets (16 pages)
    - Sketch showing uncleared areas, 1908 (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1567
      Scale: 1"=25'
    - Sketch showing changes, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1568
    - Unidentified sketch, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1570
    - Plan E of arrangement of Garden area, 1908 (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1571
    - Plan F of arrangement of Garden area, 1908 (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1572
    - Plan D of arrangement of Garden area, 1908 (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1573
    - Planting arrangement, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1574
    - Unidentified sketch, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1575
    - Plan C of arrangement of garden area, 1908 (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1576
    - Suggested change in yard, 1908 (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1577
    - Unidentified sketch - gardens likely, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1578
    - Sketches of flower boxes, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1579
    - Planting arrangement, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1580
    - Planting plan, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1581
    - Planting plan, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1582
    - Plan showing in detail arrangement about residence, 1908 (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1583
    - Map of town and village of Riverside, Illinois, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1584
      Format: Stock
    - Sketch, Undated (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1585
    - Plan for arrangement of garden area, 1908 (Box 76)
      Sheet # 1589
    - Plan showing arrangement about residence, 1908 (revised 1909) (Box 76)
      Sheet # 1590
      Format: Unspecified
    - Rider for drive alteration, 1909 (Box 76)
      Sheet # 1591
    - Planting list, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1593
    - Planting list, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1594
    - Several drawings, details, Undated; Wright, Frank Lloyd (Folder 46)
      Sheet # 1600
      Scale: Varies
      Format: Blue Linen
    - Elevation wall at carriage entrance, etc., Undated; Wright, Frank Lloyd (Folder 46)
      Sheet # 1601
    - First floor plan, Undated; Wright, Frank Lloyd (Folder 46)
      Sheet # 1602
    - East, North, and South elevations, Undated; Wright, Frank Lloyd (Folder 46)
      Sheet # 1603
      Format: Blue on Linen
    - Basement plan, Undated; Wright, Frank Lloyd (Folder 46)
      Sheet # 1604
    - West elevation, longitudinal section, Undated; Wright, Frank Lloyd (Folder 46)
      Sheet # 1605
    - Outbuilding, Undated (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1606
    - Arrangement about residence, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1607
    - Arrangement of garden area, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1608
    - Arrangement about residence, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1609
    - Plan "A" of suggested changes on property, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1610
    - Plan "B" of suggested changes on property, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1611
    - Topographical survey of block 2, First division, Riverside, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1612
    - Topographical survey of block 2, First division, Riverside, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1613
    - Topographical survey of block 2, First division, Riverside, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1614
    - Topographical survey of block 2, First division, Riverside, 1908 (Box 54)
      Sheet # 1615
    - Plot of grounds, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1751
      Condition:Very Poor
    - Plot of grounds, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1752
    - Plan D of arrangement of garden area, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1753
    - Plan F of arrangement of garden area, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1754
    - Plan E of arrangement of garden area, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1755
    - Plot of grounds, Undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1756
    - Plot of grounds, Undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
      Sheet # 1757
    - Planning plan of the garden and elevations showing espaliers, 1910 (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1798
  - Cornell University Development Location: Ithaca, New York
    - Bridge at Beebe Lake, 1929 (Box 47)
      Sheet # 1402
  - Coulby, Harry Location: Wickliffe, Ohio
    - South elevation of Residence, by architect Frederic WM. Striebinger, Undated (Box 21)
      Sheet # 517
    - Planting plan of formal garden, Undated (Folder 23)
      Sheet # 518
    - Sketches for awning and porch, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1874
    - Sketches for awning and porch, Undated (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1875
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1876
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1877
    - Steel frame for awning, 1914 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1878
    - Steel frame for awning, 1914 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1879
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1880
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1881
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1882
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1883
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1884
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1885
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1886
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 66)
      Sheet # 1887
    - East elevation, Undated (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1888
    - Section "A-A", Undated (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1889
    - Section "B-B", Undated (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1890
    - North Elevation, Undated (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1891
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1892
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1893
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1894
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1895
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1896
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1897
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1899
      Scale: 1/8"=1'; 1/4"=1'
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1900
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1901
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1902
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1903
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1904
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1905
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1906
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1907
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1908
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1909
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1910
    - North Elevation, Undated (Box 68)
      Sheet # 1911
    - Plan of fore-court, 1913 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      Sheet # 1958
    - Architectural details for garden, Undated (Folder 52)
      Sheet # 1977
  - Location: Cleveland, Ohio
    - Proposed range of glass (Greenhouse), 1913 (Box 65)
      Sheet # 1873
    - Proposed range of glass, 1913 (Box 67)
      Sheet # 1898
  - Cross, R. J. Location: Dunkirk, New York
    - House, Second floor plan, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1358
  - Curtiss, E. P. Location: Brighton, New York
    - Window details, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 730
    - Window details, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 731
    - Window details, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 732
    - Window elevations, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 733
    - Window elevations, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 734
    - Window elevations, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 735
    - Window details, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 736
      Scale: Full;1/2"=1'
    - Window elevations, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 737
    - Window elevations, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 738
  - Davis, George A. Location: Lancaster, New York
    - Balustrade elevations and plans, 1910 (Folder 23)
      Sheet # 471
      Scale: 1/4"=1'; 1 1/2"=1'
    - Details of pergola, 1910 (Folder 23)
      Sheet # 472
    - Plot plan, 1910 (Folder 23)
      Sheet # 473
    - Wall details, 1910 (Folder 23)
      Sheet # 474
  - Denison University Location: Granville, Ohio
    - Plan for arrangement and grading of portion of Campus, 1905 (Folder 10)
      Sheet # 116
      Scale: 20'=1"
      Format: Mylar, Oversized
    - Sections of area to be landscaped, 1905 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 117
      Scale: 50'=1"
    - Details of Landscape plan, 1905 (Folder 10)
      Sheet # 118
    - Topographical survey, 1905 (Folder 10)
      Sheet # 119
    - Profiles and details, 1905 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 120
    - Profiles and details, 1905 (Folder 11)
      Sheet # 121
    - Details for construction of East terminus, 1905 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 122
      Scale: 10'=1"
    - Details of Construction for East Terminus, 1905 (Folder 14)
      Sheet # 231
    - Road profiles, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 277
      Format: Gridded Tracing paper
    - Plan for arrangement, 1905 (Folder 19)
      Sheet # 279
    - Section to accompany plan no. 62-9, 1905 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1812
      Format: Blueprint (Sepia) (Negative)
    - Plan for arrangement, 1905 (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1813
  - Donner, P. E. Location: Edgeworth, Pennsylvania
    - Forecourt details, 1917 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 638
      Scale: 1/10"=1';1 1/2"=1'
    - General arrangement of property, 1916 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 642
    - Perspective of Garden, Undated (Box 33)
      Sheet # 840
  - Dunlap, Esq., D. A. Location: Toronto, Ontario
    - Quarter inch scale detail of wall, 1910 (Box 14)
      Sheet # 258
    - Garage plans, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 259
    - Garage elevations - North and South, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 260
    - Garage elevations - East and West, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 261
    - Plan of roads and walls, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 262
      Scale: 1:=15'
      Note:Fleming
    - Partial study of gardens, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 263
    - Alterations and additions to residence, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 264
    - Alterations and additions to residence, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 265
    - Sketch showing Lot lines, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 266
    - Sketch showing Lot lines, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 267
    - Alterations and additions to residence: Southwest elevation, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 268
    - Floor plan of residence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 269
    - Details of ornamental iron from Canada Foundry company, Undated (Folder 18)
      Sheet # 270
      Scale: 1/4"=1', 1"=1'
    - Survey of Property, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 271
      Scale: 1"=15'
    - Plan of arrangement, 1910 (Folder 18)
      Sheet # 272
    - Planting plan, 1910 (Folder 18)
      Sheet # 273
    - Site Plan, 1910 (Folder 18)
      Sheet # 274
      Format: Heavy paper - Cardstock, likely
      Condition:Poor - Half of drawing is missing
    - Revised detail for fence, 1910 (Folder 18)
      Sheet # 275
    - Detail of fence, Undated (Folder 18)
      Sheet # 276
      Scale: full
      Format: Watercolor on Tracing paper attached to Heavy paper like Card stock
    - Rough sketch of Garden layout, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 305
      Format: "D. A. Dunlap" Stationery
    - Rough sketches of Garden layout, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 306
    - Rough sketches of Garden layout, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 307
    - Preliminary garden arrangement, Undated (Folder 20)
      Sheet # 308
    - Sketch of carriage gate, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 309
    - Sketch of carriage gate, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 310
    - Preliminary plan showing proposed arrangement of grounds, 1910 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 311
      Format: Tracing paper with pencil and crayon
    - Full scale detail of Fence iron work, Undated (Box 15)
      Sheet # 312
    - Rough plan of layout, Undated (Box 15)
      Sheet # 313
    - Transverse section through West drive from street to garden, 1910 (Box 15)
      Sheet # 314
    - Perspective sketch of portion of Garden, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 315
    - Sketch of Elevation for Conservatory, likely, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 316
    - Sketch of house and proposed additions, likely, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 317
    - Sketch of proposed Garden Layout, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 318
    - Elevation and Plan of Conservatory, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 319
    - Rough floor plan of House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 320
    - Portion of plan for Garden arrangement, Undated (Folder 20)
      Sheet # 321
      Condition:Poor - torn and pieces missing
    - Plan of arrangement for a section of the garden, Undated (Folder 20)
      Sheet # 322
    - Quarter inch detail of wall, 1910 (Box 16)
      Sheet # 323
    - Sketch of Fence and fence post, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 324
    - Plan of roads and walls, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 325
    - Detail of fence, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 326
    - Detail of fence, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 327
    - Detail of fence, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 328
    - Plan of road paving, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 329
    - Detail of bench and wall, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 330
    - Detail of bench and wall, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 331
    - Perspective sketch of Entry gates, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 332
    - Aerial perspective sketch of Entry gates, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 333
    - Sections through paving, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 334
    - Revised quarter inch scale detail of walls, 1910 (Box 16)
      Sheet # 335
    - Detail of fence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 336
    - Typical section thought drive from street through East gate to junction with West drive, 1910 (Box 16)
      Sheet # 337
      Format: Ink on Tracing paper
    - Full scale detail of iron work for fence and gates, 1910 (Box 16)
      Sheet # 338
    - Continuation of iron fence and gates, 1910 (Box 16)
      Sheet # 339
    - Detail of iron fence and gates, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 340
    - Sketch plan of Garage court and plantings, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 341